(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Samantha was starting her first day of sixth
grade in two weeks.
She needed a new backpack.
Her backpack from last year was ripped.
This year, she wanted a cool backpack to
start off her middle school years.
She did not know where to begin.
She went to the mall and began searching.
Her mom suggested she get something with flowers.
Her dad suggested she get something plain.
However, when she saw this backpack, she knew
it was meant to be hers.
The backpack had several pockets to hold all
her belongings.
It was also made of sturdy and durable
material.
The backpack was pink with purple dots.
She immediately grabbed it and asked her mom
if she could get it.
Her mom said okay and handed her some
money.
She was very excited.